Time can dissolve all obsessions.
Years can heal all wounds in the world.
But for me,
after a thousand years,
only the old wound in my heart
has never scabbed over
and never faded.
Help me.
Stop.
Tang'er.
I thought the memories sealed deep in time
had long vanished with the wind.
But at the slightest touch,
regret,
guilt,
and remorse
surge up
and swallow me whole.
Who are you?
I am the messenger who judges good and evil
and ferries souls.
Soul.
Where is Tang'er's soul?
Can I see her one more time?
She was pure and virtuous in life,
and now rests in peace.
But you have committed too much slaughter just now,
making you unable to reincarnate,
and you will never see her again in this life.
However, throughout your mortal life,
you kept kindness in your heart,
so I
can give you a chance to see her again.
I am willing to try, no matter the cost.
You will endure boundless loneliness day and night,
and eternal torment.
Are you still willing?
Even if it means eternal torment,
as long as there is a sliver of hope to see her again,
I will have no regrets.
Since this is what your heart desires,
come with me.
From today on,
Chen Yao is dead,
and your past self is gone from this world.
You will serve under the Day and Night Wandering Gods,
and become a soul ferryman.
Using one's own pain
to warn the world that actions have consequences.
In the long years,
only by staying true to oneself
and fulfilling one's duties
can one wait for the chance
to see the one they yearn for again.
Bastard, let me go.
Okay.
As you wish.
Save my daughter.
I've searched for you for five years.
You actually showed up on your own.
That saves me a lot of trouble.
I beg you, save my daughter.
I'll do anything you ask.
I was just one step away
from avenging my father.
Mumu.
A dream.
It's a dream.
How can a dream feel so real?
It's been five years.
I finally got this chance.
I will personally send you to prison
and clear my father's name.
Morning, Lawyer Gu.
The same.
Sorry, Lawyer Gu.
Watch where you're going.
Sorry.
Thank you, Lawyer Gu.
Be careful.
Everything is the same.
Then right now,
Lingze should be in my office.
Mr. Ling, why are you here?
Waiting for you.
If you need anything, just let me know.
I would have gone to you.
Why did you come in person?
How are the preparations for the trial?
Everything is ready.
That's good.
There's one more thing
I need your help with.
Go ahead.
Right before the trial,
go get the evidence of Mu Cheng blackmailing me.
If Mu Cheng doesn't cooperate during the trial,
expose this evidence.
As for the rest,
I don't need to teach you what to do, right?
I really came back to this day.
December 1st.
The Mu Cheng case goes to trial today.
An influencer with tens of millions of followers
and the entertainment giant Ling Group are officially on trial.
The case uncovered the massive tips in livestreams
and the dark truth of illegal transactions behind them.
Is it the artist's moral failure,
or did Ling Group condone it for profit?
The red line of internet traffic must not be crossed.
This trial of the empire has the whole city's attention.
I accuse the boss of Ling Media,
Ling Ze.
He threatened and forced me
to sell my body.
Mr. Wang.
Mr. Ling, Mr. Ling.
Every time after my livestream ended,
Come.
he would use celebrating as an excuse
to take me to nightclubs to relax.
I finally get to see you in person.
Come, have a seat.
Then,
he also made me accompany investors.
Let me go.
The plaintiff defamed the defendant
and extorted them.
You're talking nonsense.
I have the plaintiff's transfer records here.
It is clear from this
that before having relations with the investor,
the plaintiff had already received his transfers.
This is a conspiracy orchestrated by her.
What is going on?
There's new evidence.
Your Honor.
I am the investor Wang mentioned by the plaintiff.
I can prove that everything the defendant said is true.
It was Mucheng who took the initiative to get close to me.
She wanted to use tricks to bring down Ling's.
Xingcan.
Let me go.
He has already forged evidence of you blackmailing him.
You can't win this lawsuit.
What did you say?
Work with me.
I have a way to get your freedom back.
Have you decided
what reward you want?
I want...
You.
Killing you would be letting you off too easy.
I will bring you to justice
and make you suffer in prison.
I got the stuff. See you at the bridge.
This
contains all the evidence of Lingze's crimes.
Keep it safe.
Appear in court at dawn tomorrow.
With this,
we can definitely bring Lingze to justice.
Let's go. I'll take you back first.
What's wrong?
You.
Let me go.
Got it.
Get the job done.
You can name your reward.
Since God gave me a second chance,
I must not fail this time.
Okay, okay, I'm already here.
I'll be right up.
No problem. No problem.